<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
        <string name="app_name">Утилизатус</string>
        <string name="greetings">Hi ;)</string>
        <string name="slogan">It is in your power to make the planet cleaner and
        brighter! So what are you waiting for?</string>
        <string name="enter">Log in</string>
        <string name="login">Login</string>
        <string name="password">Password</string>
        <string name="reg_screen">Registration</string>
        <string name="confirm_password">Confirm password</string>
        <string name="login_type">By login</string>
        <string name="pass_type">By number</string>
        <string name="otp_code">Your SMS code to log in to the app:</string>
        <string name="phone">Phone number</string>
        <string name="log_in">Log in</string>
        <string name="next">Next</string>
        <string name="pass_forgot">Forgot password?</string>
        <string name="no_code">Send the code again</string>
        <string name="enter_with">Log in with</string>
        <string name="registration">Sign up</string>
        <string name="OTP">Enter the code</string>
        <string name="OTP_phone">An SMS-code has been sent to your number</string>
        <string name="main">Main</string>
        <string name="more">More Detail</string>
        <string name="popular">Popular</string>
        <string name="bonuses">Rewards</string>
        <string name="menu">Menu</string>
        <string name="descript">Description</string>
        <string name="map">Map</string>
        <string name="begin">Start</string>
        <string name="sorting">Sort</string>
        <string name="searching">Search</string>
        <string name="awesome">Keep it up!</string>

        <string name="enter_login">Enter login</string>
        <string name="enter_password">Enter password</string>
        <string name="error_login">Invalid login or password</string>
        <string name="enter_phone">Enter phone number</string>
        <string name="error_phone">Invalid phone number</string>
        <string name="error_sms">Invalid SMS-code</string>

        <string name="item_1">Recyclable</string>
        <string name="item_2">Paper</string>
        <string name="item_3">Glass</string>
        <string name="item_4">Metal</string>
        <string name="item_5">Plastic</string>
        <string name="item_6">Food waste</string>
        <string name="item_7">Textile</string>
        <string name="item_8">Dang. waste</string>
        <string name="item_9">Build waste</string>
        <string name="item_10">Electronics</string>
        <string name="item_11">Not recyclable</string>

        <string name="card_more_1">Waste paper</string>
        <string name="card_more_2">Bottles</string>
        <string name="card_more_3">Vials</string>
        <string name="card_more_4">Metal cans</string>
        <string name="card_more_5">Cloth</string>
        <string name="card_more_6">Glass</string>
        <string name="card_more_7">Medicines</string>
        <string name="card_more_8">Appliances</string>
        <string name="card_more_9">Furniture</string>
        <string name="card_more_10">Food waste</string>
        <string name="card_more_11">Batteries</string>

        <string name="card_pop_1">Newspaper</string>
        <string name="card_pop_2">Magazine</string>
        <string name="card_pop_3">Package</string>
        <string name="card_pop_4">Wrap</string>
        <string name="card_pop_5">Clothes</string>
        <string name="card_pop_6">Telephone</string>
        <string name="card_pop_7">Footwear</string>
        <string name="card_pop_8">Tin cans</string>
        <string name="card_pop_9">Aluminum foil</string>
        <string name="card_pop_10">Incandescent lamp</string>
        <string name="card_pop_11">Paint</string>
        <string name="card_pop_12">Concrete</string>
        <string name="card_pop_13">Oil</string>
        <string name="card_pop_14">Battery</string>
        <string name="card_pop_15">Food</string>
        <string name="card_pop_16">Box</string>
        <string name="card_pop_17">Linen</string>
        <string name="card_pop_18">Wood</string>

        <string name="sorting_tip">Find out exactly how to sort garbage</string>
        <string name="searching_tip">Find out where the nearest garbage sorting point is located</string>
        <string name="awesome_tip">By sorting the garbage, you helped the planet, and also received bonuses. Keep it up!</string>

        <string name="card_pop_desc">Click to learn more</string>

        <string name="desc_1">This category includes newspapers, magazines, printer paper, cards, letters and other paper products.
                Waste paper can be recycled and used as raw materials for the production of new paper.
                With one ton of recycled waste paper, you can save 17 trees and 7,000 gallons of water.</string>

        <string name="desc_2">This category includes glass and plastic bottles.
                Glass bottles can be recycled and used over and over again without loss of quality, and plastic bottles can be recycled into many different products, including clothing and mats.
                One glass bottle, recycled instead of discarded, can illuminate a 100 watt bulb for 4 hours.</string>

        <string name="desc_3">Bottles made of glass and plastic used for medicines and cosmetic products belong to this category.
                As with bottles, glass vials can be recycled multiple times.
                Plastic bottles can be recycled as a material for making other products, including garden tools and furniture.</string>

        <string name="desc_4">This category includes aluminum and steel cans used for food preservation.
                Metal cans can be recycled and used as raw materials for the production of new cans, cars and even airplanes.
                One aluminum can can be recycled and used to produce a new can within just 60 days.</string>

        <string name="desc_5">This category includes old clothes, bed linen, towels and other textiles.
                The fabric can be recycled and used as a raw material for the production of new textiles.
                Fabric recycling can also save up to 90% of the water and energy that is used in the production of new fabric.
                Some companies also collect old clothes for recycling as insulation for homes and buildings.</string>

        <string name="desc_6">This category includes glass bottles, windows, mirrors and other glass products.
                Glass can be recycled and used as a raw material for the production of new glass, while reducing the amount of raw materials and energy needed.
                One ton of recycled glass can save up to 1.2 tons of raw materials and 130 kg of carbon dioxide.</string>

        <string name="desc_7">This category includes expired or unnecessary medicines that need to be disposed of in a safe way.
                Medicines should not be thrown into the trash, because they can cause pollution of water resources and danger to human and animal health.
                Some pharmacies and hospitals provide an opportunity to donate outdated medicines for safe disposal.</string>

        <string name="desc_8">This category includes old computers, phones, televisions and other electronic devices.
                Disposal of electronics requires a special approach, because they may contain dangerous chemicals.
                Many companies accept the recycling of electronics and recycle it, using valuable resources such as gold, silver and copper as raw materials for the production of new devices.</string>

        <string name="desc_9">This category includes old or damaged furniture that must be disposed of in a safe way.
                Furniture may contain toxic chemicals that can pollute the environment if thrown into a landfill.
                Many companies offer furniture recycling services, as well as recycle it as raw materials for the production of new furniture products.</string>

        <string name="desc_10">This category includes food leftovers that can be disposed of by composting.
                Composting is the process of processing organic waste into nutritious soil. Compost can be used as fertilizer for plants and gardens.
                Composting food waste can also reduce the amount of waste that ends up in landfill.</string>

        <string name="desc_11">This category includes old or unwanted batteries that must be disposed of in a safe way.
                Batteries may contain toxic chemicals that can cause environmental pollution if disposed of in landfills.
                Some companies offer battery recycling services, as well as collect them for recycling and using valuable materials such as zinc and manganese.</string>
</resources>